> > Brian Holt: 现在我们在这里有宠物，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what's really good about
this now is we have pets up here, right?
这代表了一组我们从 API中回来的宠物。
And this represents a set of pets
that we've gotten back from the API.
现在我要在这里制造另一个组件
Now, I'm gonna create
another component here.
>> Brian Holt: 您可以除去该控制台日志。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: You can get
rid of that console log.
>> Brian Holt: 在表单下面，我们会创建一些已调用的内容
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Underneath the form here,
we're gonna create something called
结果，我们只会在宠物中通过，所以宠物 = 。
Results, and we're just gonna
pass in pets, so pets = .
> > Brian Holt: 然后在上面，在顶部，我们会说，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then up here,
at the top, we're gonna say,
从 "./Results" 导入结果。
import results from './Results'.
同样，我们还没有创造这一领域，但我们即将开始。
Again, we haven't created this yet,
but we're about to.
因此，第 3 行， whoops， >> Brian Holt: 导入结果
So, line 3, whoops,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: import results
来自 "./Results"。
from './Results'.
所以我们把它放进去
So we put that in.
> > Brian Holt: 然后在下面，我们把结果放在
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then down here,
we put Results with
宠物=，第 54 行。
pets=, there on line 54.
我们即将开始创造新的
And we're about to go create this new
文件， >> Brian Holt: And
file,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
开始以有用的方式展示我们的宠物
start displaying our pets in a useful way.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，请保存。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, save that.
名为 results.js 的新文件。
New file called results.js.
贡纳进口反应
Gonna import react
从 " React"开始。
from 'React'.
从 "./Pet" 导入 Pet 。
Import Pet from './Pet'.
如果你还记得我们第一次做的事就是创造宠物
If you remember, one the very first things
we did in the course was create the Pet
组件，我们会重复使用。
component, we're gonna reuse that.
我要说的是 const 结果 = (，
And here, I'm gonna say,
const Results = (,
>> Brian Holt: Whops 双箭头。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Whops double arrow.
然后我们就回去了
Then we're going to return.
> > Brian Holt: 在这里，我们要做一些标记。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
here we're just gonna do a bit of markup.
我们会说 div className="search"。
So, we're gonna say div
className="search".
>> Brian Holt: 我们会说，如果 pets.length === 0，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're gonna say,
if pets.length === 0,
我们会用三元的
and we're gonna use the ternary.
因此，如果它没有长度，那么表示尚未从 API 返回任何结果，
So if it has no length, which means no
results have come back from the API yet,
我们要返回的是一个 h1 ，上面说没有佩茨。
what we're going to return is
an h1 that says, No Pets Found.
好吧否则我们就得回去了
Okay, otherwise we're going
to return something that
会显示所有的宠物对吧
displays all the pets, right?
所以我们会说地图我们要带宠物
So we're gonna say, pets.map,
and we're gonna take in a pet and
我们要把它从它的部分中取出来
we're going to make a Pet
component out of it.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我们需要做动物 =。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we need to do animal =.
再记得，这些都是从 API来的。
And again, remember,
these are coming from the API.
>> Brian Holt: 对不起，你得做一个宠物组件，宠物。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Sorry, rather,
you have to make a Pet component, Pet.
> > Brian Holt: 在这里我要说动物，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
inside of here I'm gonna say animal,
>> Brian Holt: =。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: =.
>> Brian Holt: 我想说，键=。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm gonna say,
key=.
>> Brian Holt: 名称=。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: name=.
>> Brian Holt: 品种=。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: breed=.
>> Brian Holt: media=。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: media=.
>> Brian Holt: location=，我将使用模板字符串，因此
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: location=,
I'm gonna use template strings, so
就在那边的后院对吧
the backticks there, right?
> > Brian Holt: 我们会
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're gonna
表示 $，
say $,
$ 。
$.
最后，我们需要标识，它将等于 。
And then lastly, we need the ID,
which will be equal to .
> > Brian Holt: 好的，这样就可以了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so that'll do that.
再一次，这张地图，所以这个要回来了，
Again, this is a map, so
this is going to return, for
我从 API 中得到的每一个宠物都能提供一个宠物组件
every pet that I get back from the API,
it will give back one Pet component.
如果它找不到任何东西，那么它就会说，没有宠物发现。
And if it can't find anything,
then it'll just say, No Pets Found.
现在，让这件事变得更成熟是件好事，对吧 ?
Now, it would be good to make
this more sophisticated, right?
如果有一个好的装载指示器和类似的东西会更好。
It would be better if this had a nice
loading indicator and things like that.
这不是我们今天要做的事
That's not something we're gonna do today,
but
显然你能做到最好的 UX
there's obviously better UX
that you could do about this.
再次记住我们要把宠物养在这里
So again,
remember we're getting pets here,
这是从父母来的对吧
this is coming from the parent, right?
我们在父母中搜寻宠物
S we search for the pets in the parent,
然后我们把它传给子组件对吧
and then we pass that down into
the child component, right?
这是 React中的关键模式。
This is a key pattern in React.
这是一个关键模式 React ，因为您有从父级流向子代的数据，
It's a key pattern React because you
have data flowing from parent to child,
孩子和孩子的孩子对吧
child to its child and
child to its child, right?
所以，这些数据是向下流动的。
So it's this data that flows down.
但是通知不会流的对吧
But notice it doesn't flow up, right?
这称为单向数据流。
This is called one-way data flow.
这真的很有用，因为如果我有个搜索参数的问题，
This is really, really useful, because
if I have a problem with search params,
我知道问题不是源于它的任何一个儿童组件，对吗 ?
I know that problem is not arising from
any of its child components, right?
所以它不是因结果而产生的，它不是由 Pet产生的，
So it's not arising from Result,
it's not arising from Pet,
因为当父代影响子代时，子代无法影响其父代。
because while the parent can affect the
child, the child cannot affect its parent.
它甚至不知道自己的父母是谁
It doesn't even know who its parent is.
>> Brian Holt: 再次，这种感觉限制了一些时尚，但
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Again,
this feels limiting in some fashions, but
最终实际上是非常有用的。
in the end it actually ends
up being extremely useful.
因为如果我有虫子我知道从何开始
Because if I have any bugs,
I know where to start.
这很有帮助
And that's super helpful.
>> Brian Holt: 现在我说它只流一个，只能
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now I say that it only
flows one way and it can only possibly
以某种方式流，实际上有一些方法可以逆转这一流程。
flow for some way, there actually
are some ways to reverse that flow.
而且是故意的，因为大多数时候你不应该
And it's intentionally difficult, because
most of the time you should not and
不需要。
do not need to.
它真的只对图书馆的作者有用，对吧 ?
It's actually really only useful for
library authors, right?
像雷法路由器之类的人
So someone like React Router or
something like.
最重要的是，这不是你应该采用的模式。
For the most part, that's not
a pattern that you should be adopting.
>> Brian Holt: 但在中间 React 中，我将向您展示。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But in intermediate React,
I'll show you how.
最后，请确保您完成，导出缺省结果。
Last thing down here, make sure you do,
export default Results.
省省吧
Save that.
> > Brian Holt: 然后你就可以回来了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And then you should
be able to come back over here.
你可能有某种错误
You might have some sort of error,
只要刷新页面可能就会消失在包裹里
just refresh the page,
it probably will go away from Parcel.
> > Brian Holt: 好的，我要点击 " Submit" 。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so,
I'm just gonna hit Submit.
你可以在这里看到，现在我从 API那里得到了真实的结果。
And you can see here, now I'm getting
real results back from the API.
所以我们有胖子 Slim 和 Cindy 和霍莉
So we have Fatboy Slim and
Cindy and Holly.
> > Brian Holt: 看来这些大多是狗。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
looks like these are mostly dogs.
> > Brian Holt: 但你也应该能找到猫。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
you should be able to find cats as well.
那是只搜寻狗的线索
That's cuz it is only searching for dogs.
所以它在做它的工作。
So it's doing its job.
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 但我们可以切换到猫身上，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: But
we're able there to switch to cats, right?
现在这些也是猫的领养方式。
And now these are cats to adopt as well.